SYED RIZWAN KHAN

Wordpress Developer

U 03132505278

- @ syedrizwankhan98@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/syed-rizwan-khan/
- Plat No.305, Burj-ul-Ameen, NazimabadNo.4, Karachi



SUMMARY

A talented IT professional with a passion for tailored solutions seeks the position of WordPress Developer in a thriving, exciting, and growing company. Comes with a Bachelor's degree in Software Engineering and more than two years of experience in Frontend Development.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) Software Engineering

USMAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY

2016 - 2020

EXPERIENCE

Senior WordPress Developer

Legacy World BPO Private Limited

05/2022 - Ongoing

- Covert Designs from XD to HTML5, Bootstrap and WordPress.
- Provided guidance and leadership to junior developers.

Frontend Developer

SourceCode

1 03/2022 - 05/2022

· Covert Designs from XD to HTML and WordPress.

WordPress Developer

Core Cut Solutions

1 05/2021 - 02/2022

• Convert Designs from PSD to WordPress and PSD to HTML.

Junior WordPress Developer

CentoSquare

1 01/2021 - 05/2021

Created Web Layouts using HTML and CSS.

SKILLS

HTML5

CSS3

Javascript

WordPress

Woocommerce

PSD/XD to WordPress

PSD/XD to HTML

CERTIFICATES

HTML Essential Training - LinkedIn

Issued Sep 2022

CSS: Animation - LinkedIn

Issued Sep 2022

Cutting-Edge CSS - LinkedIn

Issued Sep 2022

CSS - HackerRank

Issued Aug 2022

CSS Essential Training - LinkedIn

Issued Jul 2022

Frontend Development - Interns Pakistan

Issued Feb 2021